# 它們都 關不住它們啦 跑出來啦
They all, I can't fence them off anymore. They're all running out.
# 啊 倒在地上給你們吃 算啦
Ah! Alright, alright. I spill them all onto the ground for you.
# 倒點你身上
Some is on your bodies.
# 現在它們都會跑出
Now they all know how to run away.
# 關不住啦
I can't fence them off anymore.
# 想個辦法才行
I gotta figure out a solution.
# 哇 在那邊的都來啦 (註︰我聽到的卻是「其他的都來了」)
Wa! The rest are also coming,
# 跑得好快呀
running very fast.
# 你看 小豬
Look! The piggies,
# 都是玩泥巴啦 在上面玩水
they're always playing in the mud and in the water.
# 搞得一身都髒不拉稀的 都不像豬
Simply gross! They don't even look like pigs.
# 像野豬
They look like wild pigs.
# 吃得好歡啊
They're eating so merrily.
# 好不好吃
Does it taste good?
# 那麼怕我幹嘛 我只坐著看你們吃
Why are you so scared of me? I'm just sitting here and watching you eat.
# 看你吃得那麼香
You know, you enjoy the food so much.
# 好好吃哦 過年我吃你們的肉
Eat well! I'll have your pork during the Chinese New Year.
# 那麼胖
So fat!
# 一下子就被吃完啦
It's eaten up in just a second.
# 馬上就快沒有啦
There's nearly nothing left already.
# 吞得太快啦 都嗆到它啦
It gets chocked. It's eating too fast.
# 小狗
Doggy
# 趴在我腳上 趴在我大腿上
Lean on my leg! Lean on my thigh!
# 沒啦
No more!
# 你看 這個大公豬 上次你還拱我
Look! This big boar. You attacked me last time.
# 我對你多好哇
But you see how well I treat you?
# 現在還給飯給你吃
I still give you food now.
# 要聽話 好好帶崽
Be a good pig! Take good care of your children!
# 不能老是跑上來
You shouldn't come down all the time.
# 跑上來 過年 過年我就把
If you come again, during, during the Chinese New Year, I'll turn you,
# 把你做成臘肉 或者把你做成香腸
turn you into cured pork, or turn you into sausages.
# 小豬崽 小豬崽
Little piglets, little piglets
# 一下就被它們吃完啦
It's eaten up in just a second.
# 捉不到它啦
There's no way to catch them now.
# 我一動身它就跑
They simply run away whenever I move a muscle.
# 你看 這條肚子那麼大一個
Look! This pig has such an enormous belly.
# 快貼地上啦
It's almost touching the ground.
# 好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
# 豬都餵完啦
Now the pigs have been fed.
# 個個長得一身肥膘
Everyone is completely covered with fat.
# 你看 這條跟這條 好肥呀
Look! This one and this one. Really fat!
# 母豬就比較瘦
But the sow is a bit skinny.